

ROHAYU BINTI JAJULI



PERSONAL DETAILS



No 287, Lorong 2 Jalan Laksamana, Desa Maju Sungai

Tengi, 44010, Kuala Kubu Bharu, Selangor.

D.O.B: 15 Jan 1993 Gender: Female Licenses: B2/D Tel: +60175357467

E-mail: rohayujajuli@gmail.com



CAREER OBJECTIVES

To expand own career scope as well as gaining precious experience in an international organization with promising opportunity to optimize own skills & competency by adapting applicable knowledge of Quality Management System, Project Management, and Problem Solving.



EDUCATION

BACHELOR MANUFACTURING ENGINEERING (HONS.)

Universiti Malaysia Perlis(UniMAP), 2012-2016

CGPA: 2.75/4.00

SCIENCE STREAM

Kolej Matrikulasi Selangor, 2011-2012

CGPA: 2.76/4.00.

SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA (SPM)

Sekolah Menengah Kebangsaan Ungku Aziz, 2005-

SPM: 1A+ 2A 1A- 2B+ 2C+



LANGUAGES

Language	Spoken	Writing
Malay	****	****
English	****	****



SKILLS

**** Microsoft Office/Excel/Powerpoint **** AutoCAD ******** CATIA V5 **** Geomagic Control (3D scanner)

Coordinate Measuring Machine (CMM)

EXPERIENCES

QUALITY INSPECTOR, (Industrial Quality Management Sdn. Bhd, IQMSB-Bukit Beruntung)

Duration: Aug 2016- Present

- 3D scanner incharge
- **Conduct Penetration test**
- Monitoring product quality level
- Oganizing new product document preparation & trial inspection
- Monitoring product quality level and rejection in daily production

INTERNSHIP, (Volvo Car Manufacturing- Shah Alam)

Duration: June 2015- Sep 2015

- Study standardization of work by taking the cycle time of car assembly.
- Involving quality control and quality assurance by detecting car's defect from stations involved and ensure those car does not pass through inspection station.

FINAL YEAR PROJECT, (Mediguip Sdn Bhd - Perlis)

Duration: Nov 2015- June 2016

Improving process of catheter production from manually eye burning process to staggered eye punching process.



REFERENCE

PROF.MADYA DR. KHAIRUL AZWAN ISMAIL (DEAN OF MANUFACTURING ENGINEERING SCHOOL)

+60 19 -5110111